# Pham Thi Ngoc Quynh

# Front-end Developer

(+84) 393 947 577
phthingocquynh@gmail.com
behance.net/quynhphamthingoc

I am a highly motivated and creative front-end developer with strong passion for UX. Having a good understanding of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, however I would never stop learning new technologies. I am not only be able to work independently but also as part of a team, and willing to help others. I believe that I can use my skills and experiences to help you create user-friendly and engaging websites. I am a hard-worker who always willing to go the extra miles.

## **Education & Certificate**

University of Science - VNUHCM

**Information Technology** 

2017 - 2021

DIA ACADEMY, HCMC

UI/UX Designer

2022

#### **Skills**

- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- ReactJS
- · Restful API
- UI libraries: Bootstrap, Tailwind
- UI/UX Research & Design

- Communication
- Teamwork
- · Problem-Solving
- · Analytical Thinking

## **Experience**

## Front-end Developer | WinTech JSC, HCMC

Apr 2022 - Apr 2023

- Built a design system for the company, which included design principles, components, and templates. The
  design system was used to create a consistent and scalable user experience across all of the company's
  products.
- Designed a landing page for a company's website, improving brand awareness by providing visitors with information about the company and its products or services. This resulted in a 20% increase in conversions.
- Analyzed requirements, designed and Developed an E-coaching application for my company's leadership coaches, which allows the coaching process to be delivered effectively and efficiently to each individual.
- Developed a web-based human resources management (HRM) application to help the HR department manage human resources more efficiently, saving time and resources for the company.
- Proactively communicate with teams to ensure efficient and timely delivery of projects.
- · Technologies: ReactJS, Tailwind.

## Front-end Developer | Thang Loi Group, HCMC

Dec 2020 - Apr 2022

- Collaborated with the Marketing team to build the E-Thiep application, which personalizes and automatically sends invitations with QR codes for check-in, mini-games, and enhances the customer experience at sales events.
- Developed applications to serve customer care, management, and internal operations:
  - Call Center: Developed a call center system that manages calls and customer call-related information. This
    system helps the company's Customer Service department to take care of customers more easily and
    effectively.
  - BaseCRM: Developed a customer relationship management (CRM) system that manages customer data in a central place. This system provides the ability to store, track, and validate customer data, optimize customer engagement, and build better relationships.
  - Asset Management: Developed an asset management system that manages, catalogs, tracks, and maintains an company's assets. This system helps the company to track the location and condition of its assets, ensure that assets are properly maintained.
- Technologies: HTML, Bootstrap, Javascript.

- Developed a landing page for a company's website and mobile application an individual assistant aims to financial management and give advice.
- Technologies: NextJS; React Native.

## **Software Project**

### Thang Loi Fun Run's Landing Page

trieubuocchanhanhphuc.vn

Outsource Project

- A website that hosts a running challenge for the community.
- The website includes features such as registration, login, runner teams, summary running stats for each user, and a ranking system.
- The website has been used by over 1,000 users and has helped to motivate people to get active and improve their running performance.
- · Team size: 04.
- · Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript.

### Tan Son Nhat International Airport Customer Rating

tia.wincore.asia/customer-review

Outsource Project

- A web application that collects customer feedback (1-5 stars) on a variety of service criteria.
- Feedback can be submitted in a variety of formats (text, audio, video).
- Connect to third-party APIs to retrieve real-time flight information and provide directions to necessary service points.
- Compatible with a variety of devices (desktop, tablet, mobile).
- Supports English and Vietnamese.
- The project has been rolled out at Tan Son Nhat International Airport.
- Team size: 05.
- Technologies: ReactJS, Tailwind.

Languages	
-----------	--

## **English:**

Reading & research.

Basic communication.

#### **Tools**

- Git/Github
- VS CodeFigma
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Notion
- Jira

#### Reference

## Mr. Vo Duc Thang

CTO - Thang Loi Group

Provide if required.